module.exports = [
  {
    question:
      'Who won the Academy Award for Best Actor for his role in the movie "Lincoln" (2012)?',
    correctAnswer: "Daniel Day-Lewis",
    wrongAnswers: ["Hugh Jackman", "Joaquin Phoenix", "Denzel Washington"],
  },
  {
    question:
      'What is the name of the character played by Tom Hanks in the movie "Forrest Gump" (1994)?',
    correctAnswer: "Forrest Gump",
    wrongAnswers: ["Lt. Dan Taylor", "Bubba Blue", "Jenny Curran"],
  },
  {
    question: 'Who directed the movie "Schindler\'s List" (1993)?',
    correctAnswer: "Steven Spielberg",
    wrongAnswers: [
      "Martin Scorsese",
      "Francis Ford Coppola",
      "Quentin Tarantino",
    ],
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the name of the movie in which Heath Ledger won the Academy Award for Best Supporting Actor?",
    correctAnswer: "The Dark Knight (2008)",
    wrongAnswers: [
      "Brokeback Mountain (2005)",
      "A Knight's Tale (2001)",
      "Monster's Ball (2001)",
    ],
  },
  {
    question:
      'Which actress won the Academy Award for Best Actress for her role in "Silver Linings Playbook" (2012)?',
    correctAnswer: "Jennifer Lawrence",
    wrongAnswers: ["Meryl Streep", "Cate Blanchett", "Brie Larson"],
  },
  {
    question:
      'What is the name of the character played by Leonardo DiCaprio in the movie "The Wolf of Wall Street" (2013)?',
    correctAnswer: "Jordan Belfort",
    wrongAnswers: ["J.B. Bernstein", "Jack Dawson", "Jay Gatsby"],
  },
  {
    question: 'Who directed the movie "A Star is Born" (2018)?',
    correctAnswer: "Bradley Cooper",
    wrongAnswers: ["Clint Eastwood", "Steven Spielberg", "David O. Russell"],
  },
  {
    question:
      'What is the name of the character played by Morgan Freeman in the movie "The Shawshank Redemption" (1994)?',
    correctAnswer: 'Ellis Boyd "Red" Redding',
    wrongAnswers: ["Red", "Red Redding", "Ellis Boyd Red"],
  },
  {
    question: 'Who directed the movie "The Shawshank Redemption"',
    correctAnswer: "Frank Darabont",
    wrongAnswers: ["Steven Spielberg", "Martin Scorsese", "Quentin Tarantino"],
  },
  {
    question: "Which movie won the Academy Award for Best Picture in 2016?",
    correctAnswer: "Spotlight",
    wrongAnswers: ["La La Land", "Manchester by the Sea", "Arrival"],
  },
  {
    question:
      'Who played the lead role in the movie "The Pursuit of Happiness" (2008)?',
    correctAnswer: "Will Smith",
    wrongAnswers: ["Jaden Smith", "Thandie Newton", "Gabriele Muccino"],
  },
  {
    question: 'Who directed the movie "The Social Network" (2010)?',
    correctAnswer: "David Fincher",
    wrongAnswers: ["Martin Scorsese", "Steven Spielberg", "Christopher Nolan"],
  },
  {
    question: "Which movie is based on a novel by F. Scott Fitzgerald?",
    correctAnswer: "The Great Gatsby (2013)",
    wrongAnswers: [
      "Tender Is the Night (1962)",
      "The Last Tycoon (1976)",
      "The Curious Case of Benjamin Button (2008)",
    ],
  },
  {
    question: 'Who played the lead role in the movie "Dead Poets Society"?',
    correctAnswer: "Robin Williams",
    wrongAnswers: ["Ethan Hawke", "Robert Sean Leonard", "Josh Charles"],
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which movie stars Emma Stone and Ryan Gosling as the lead actors?",
    correctAnswer: "La La Land (2015)",
    wrongAnswers: [
      "Crazy, Stupid, Love (2011)",
      "Gangster Squad (2013)",
      "The Nice Guys (2016)",
    ],
  },
  {
    question:
      'What is the name of the character played by Sandra Bullock in the movie "The Blind Side" (2009)?',
    correctAnswer: "Leigh Anne Tuohy",
    wrongAnswers: ["Michael Oher", "Sandra Tuohy", "Lily Collins"],
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which movie stars Tim Robbins and Morgan Freeman as inmates in a prison?",
    correctAnswer: "The Shawshank Redemption (1994)",
    wrongAnswers: [
      "The Green Mile (1999)",
      "The Last Castle (2001)",
      "Escape Plan (2013)",
    ],
  },
  {
    question:
      'In the movie "The Godfather" (1972), what is the name of the youngest son of Vito Corleone?',
    correctAnswer: "Michael Corleone",
    wrongAnswers: ["Fredo Corleone", "Sonny Corleone", "Tom Hagen"],
  },
  {
    question: 'Who directed the movie "The Godfather"?',
    correctAnswer: "Francis Ford Coppola",
    wrongAnswers: ["Martin Scorsese", "Steven Spielberg", "Quentin Tarantino"],
  },
  {
    question: "Which movie won the Academy Award for Best Picture in 2009?",
    correctAnswer: "Slumdog Millionaire",
    wrongAnswers: ["Avatar", "Up in the Air", "Inglourious Basterds"],
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which movie is based on the real-life story of mathematician John Nash?",
    correctAnswer: "A Beautiful Mind (2001)",
    wrongAnswers: [
      "Good Will Hunting (1997)",
      "The Imitation Game (2014)",
      "The Theory of Everything (2014)",
    ],
  },
  {
    question: "What is the highest ranked Drama on IMDb?",
    correctAnswer: "The Shawshank Redemption (1994)",
    wrongAnswers: [
      "The Godfather (1972)",
      "The Dark Knight (2008)",
      "The Godfather: Part II (1974)",
    ],
  },

  {
    question:
      "From which movie is the quote: “My mama always said life was like a box of chocolates. You never know what you're gonna get.”?",
    correctAnswer: "Forrest Gump (1994)",
    wrongAnswers: [
      "The Green Mile (1999)",
      "The Curious Case of Benjamin Button (2008)",
      "Cast Away (2000)",
    ],
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which movie stars Tom Cruise as a sports agent who is fired and starts his own company?",
    correctAnswer: "Jerry Maguire (1996)",
    wrongAnswers: ["Top Gun (1986)", "Cocktail (1988)", "The Firm (1993)"],
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which movie stars Brad Pitt and Morgan Freeman as detectives investigating a serial killer?",
    correctAnswer: "Se7en (1995)",
    wrongAnswers: [
      "The Silence of the Lambs (1991)",
      "Zodiac (2007)",
      "Kiss the Girls (1997)",
    ],
  },
  {
    question: 'Who directed the 1999 movie "American Beauty"?',
    correctAnswer: "Sam Mendes",
    wrongAnswers: ["Steven Spielberg", "Martin Scorsese", "James Cameron"],
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which movie stars Naomi Watts and Laura Harring as two women who become involved in a mysterious conspiracy?",
    correctAnswer: "Mulholland Drive (2001)",
    wrongAnswers: [
      "Memento (2000)",
      "Lost Highway (1997)",
      "Blue Velvet (1986)",
    ],
  },
  {
    question: 'Who directed the 1994 movie "Pulp Fiction"?',
    correctAnswer: "Quentin Tarantino",
    wrongAnswers: ["Joel Coen", "David Lynch", "Wes Anderson"],
  },
  {
    question: "Which movie is based on a novel by Kazuo Ishiguro?",
    correctAnswer: "Never Let Me Go (2010)",
    wrongAnswers: [
      "Atonement (2007)",
      "The Remains of the Day (1993)",
      "The English Patient (1996)",
    ],
  },
  {
    question:
      '"I want you to draw me like one of your French girls." Which movie features this famous line?',
    correctAnswer: "Titanic (1997)",
    wrongAnswers: [
      "The Shawshank Redemption (1994)",
      "The Godfather (1972)",
      "The Dark Knight (2008)",
    ],
  },
];
